[{"question": " y'know, i can't believe i'm getting my nails done! and you said it was gonna be fun!  which it kinda is. also, you said there would be other guys here. there are no other guys here!", "answer": " chandler, there\u0092s a guy right over there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " that\u0092s a mailman! that\u0092s our mailman!   hi. how are ya?", "answer": " chandler, don\u0092t worry! this doesn\u0092t make you any less of a guy!  that does!  what am i sitting on?  i hate to think what this woman was scratching when this broke off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " hey, you know who used to have nails like that?", "answer": " hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " joey let me ask you a question. what does this light switch do?", "answer": " ohh, nothing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " didn\u0092t it drive you crazy to have a switch and not know what it did?", "answer": " i know what it did! nothing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " they wouldn\u0092t have put it there if it didn\u0092t do something! how can you not care?", "answer": " like this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " well, here\u0092s another question for ya. uhh, do you know what that silver knob on the toilet does?", "answer": " sure! it flushes it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " okay, good. now that since you know, when you come over would you mind actually using it?", "answer": "  hello!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " guess who we ran into today?!", "answer": " janice?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " isn\u0092t this amazing?", "answer": " how have you been?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " oh well, i\u0092m divorced.", "answer": " ohhh, wow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " and there it is.", "answer": " i just came up to say, \"hi!\" hi!  and you, sweetie, i\u0092ll see you tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " okay. bye.", "answer": " bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " bye.", "answer": " bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " bye.", "answer": " bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " b-bye!", "answer": " bye-bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " what?! i thought you were crazy about her!", "answer": " yeah, i know, but all of those little annoying things she did before we fell in love? like her voice, her laugh, her personality\u0097well, they\u0092re all back! y\u0092know? and she\u0092s picked up like nine new ones!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " so what are you doing bringing her here?! there\u0092s people here!", "answer": " don\u0092t worry about it. i\u0092m taking care of it tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " you are not. you have never been able to break up with her.", "answer": "  well, i don\u0092t have to break up with her this time. we\u0092re not involved! i\u0092m going to do a pre-emptive strike! i\u0092m going to end it with her before it starts. my ass is like frozen!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " i can\u0092t believe you really walk alone here! i mean, you hear such stories about new york.", "answer": " no, it\u0092s really not that bad. i mean, i-i for one, feel perfectly safe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " help! help!! help! help!!", "answer": " no, no, no ross! ross, these are friends of mine from home.  liam, devon, this is ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " hey, mate.", "answer": " how are ya man?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " oh hey, that was a good one, huh?  help! help!", "answer": " so how are you? i\u0092ve been meaning to ring you ever since i arrived but umm, well, i\u0092ve been rather busy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " do you realise that we have not seen each other since the night of that u2 concert?", "answer": " oh my god. i think you\u0092re right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": "  well, actually the last time you and i saw each other was that morning.", "answer": " oh, liam.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " oh, liam. so uh, what, were you guys playing soccer or something\u0097or should i call it  football?", "answer": " we were playing rugby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " in fact we\u0092re playing a game at the park tomorrow. you\u0092re welcome to play too if you want.", "answer": "  ross play rugby? i don\u0092t think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " what\u0092s ah, what\u0092s so funny about that?", "answer": " well i mean, you\u0092re american to start with. you don\u0092t even have rugby here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " well, we didn\u0092t have freedom here until 1776, either so\u009a", "answer": " so good then! we\u0092ll see you at riverside park at 2:00! cheers!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " cheers!", "answer": " cheers!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " oh boy, i just love to sing!", "answer": " yes, i-i know that you do, but i think one of the reasons people were complaining though, was that they paid to hear the actor sing old man river.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": "  okay, we have to talk. i\u0092m just getting out of a very serious relationship\u009a", "answer": " i know! and i\u0092m just getting out of a marriage, i mean talk about meant to be!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " right! i just think that this is happening too soon.", "answer": " oh, too soon, too schmoon. face it honey, i am not letting you get away this time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " i hear ya.  but! unfortunately, my company is transferring me overseas!", "answer": " oh no! where to?  too paris?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " no! no! not, paris. janice:too london? no-no, rome? vienna? ooh-ooh, barcelona?", "answer": " okay, could you just stop talking for a second?  yemen. that\u0092s right, yes, i\u0092m being transferred to yemen!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " when?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know exactly.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " ugh, well i will just have to soak up every once of chandler bing until that moment comes.", "answer": " but i do know that it\u0092s some time tomorrow.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " done?", "answer": " yep!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey! what\u0092s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " this switch thing has been driving me crazy. so i turned it off and checked every outlet. now, four of them don\u0092t work. which means, one of them has to be controlled by the switch. so, i plugged in things in all four of the outlets that-that make noise, so that way, when i turn it on i just follow the noise and find out which one it is.", "answer": "  i bet i stopped listening before you did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " y\u0092know, you-you also could\u0092ve used uh, lamps and then followed the light.", "answer": " yeah, well, i\u0092m using noise. okay. all right! so, is everybody ready? here we go.  i hear something! i hear something! where is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " it\u0092s coming from joey!", "answer": " oh my god, that\u0092s so freaky! turn him off!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " ooh, hey, could we put on the news? i think it might be raining.", "answer": " oh, just hold on a second. i\u0092m watching this rugby thing on espn. i don\u0092t know what the big deal is. i\u0092m man enough to play this sport.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " dude, you\u0092re not even man enough to order the channel that carries the sport.", "answer": "  hey there ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": "  janice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " y\u0092know uh, you didn\u0092t really have to help me pack.", "answer": " ohh, well when you said all you were going to be doing between now and the time you leave is packing, you didn\u0092t really leave me much choice. did you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " well, i-i thought i did but, i-i guess i did not!", "answer": " hey-hey, what\u0092s going on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " oh, i\u0092m packing. y\u0092know i\u0092m-i\u0092m packing \u0091cause i\u0092m moving to yemen tomorrow.", "answer": " thanks for telling me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " i\u0092m only going to pretend i\u0092m moving to yemen, it\u0092s the only way i can get rid off her.", "answer": " ohhhh, good one! and yemen that actually sounds like a real country.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": "  chandler! come on, i\u0092m gonna show how to roll up your underwear and stuff it in your shoes. it\u0092s a real space saver.", "answer": " yeah, i know, i do that \u0091cause it makes me look taller.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " okay, chandler, come on!", "answer": "  okay.  joey, trade lives with me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " nope.  man look at this! ross, i can\u0092t believe you said you\u0092d play rugby. i mean look how brutal this is!", "answer": " hey, i can handle it! all right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " please, ross, you-you got hurt playing badminton with my dad.", "answer": " that\u0092s \u0091cause-\u0091cause you\u0092re mom\u0092s dog kept-kept looking at me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": "  okay, ross, look-look-look-look, look right here. that\u0092s called a scrum, okay? it\u0092s kinda like a huddle.", "answer": " and is a hum, kinda like a scruddle?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " ross!  they\u0092re gonna kill you!", "answer": " well, why are you doing this anyway?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " well, you should\u0092ve seen the guy that she used to go out with. i mean, he\u0092s like joe rugby.", "answer": " you\u0092re kidding! and he plays rugby?! that\u0092s so funny.  ohh! i see how you did that. all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " anyway, she thought the very idea of me playing rugby with him was like hilarious. so i\u0092m gonna show her how tough i really am!", "answer": "  i\u0092m sorry. i\u0092m sorry. you\u0092re right, you are a tough guy. you\u0092re the toughest palaeontologist i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " all right, come on look, ross can take care of himself! it\u0092s not like he\u0092s\u009achandler!", "answer": "  thanks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " oh!", "answer": " oh, well maybe there was a dog lookin\u0092 at him.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " ross-ross-ross-ross! stay away from that guy , and that guy . and that one\u0097dude! they\u0092re all huge!", "answer": " they don\u0092t look any bigger than me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " well, maybe that\u0092s because you\u0092re closer to you. so you look bigger to you from where you are.", "answer": " i\u0092m just going to say hi to the lads. all right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " all right.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " okay, i know what i have to do. i\u0092ve got to go red ross.  y\u0092know, red ross!", "answer": " i totally don\u0092t know what you\u0092re talking about.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " come on! the time we were all waiting in line for dances with wolves and that one guy cut in line in front of us and i just lost it?! screamed at him! turned all red! red ross!!", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " liam, do me a favour. tell the lads to go easy on ross, it\u0092s his first time.", "answer": " you don\u0092t say!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " you\u009aare\u009anot going to believe it! joshua came into work today, and guess what happened?", "answer": " he asked you out?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " no. but i was showing him some cufflinks and i felt his pulse.", "answer": " saucy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": "  what are these?", "answer": " electrical plans for the building.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " okay, okay, okay should i be scared?", "answer": " i know that switch does something, okay? so-so i went down to city hall and got these. all i had to do was pay $25 and wait in line for three hours.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " y\u0092know you, really didn\u0092t have to take me to the airport.", "answer": " oh please. every moment is precious. y\u0092know? besides, somebody had to ride in that other taxi with the rest of your luggage, and your friends don\u0092t really seem to care too much that you\u0092re leaving.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " well, we\u0092re really not that close.  okay, so i guess this is uh, good-bye then.", "answer": " on no! no! it\u0092s not good-bye, i\u0092m not leaving until you get on that plane.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " okay. then i guess it\u0092s just, wait here then.   hi. i need one fake ticket to yemen. ticket counter attendant: one ticket to yemen?", "answer": " oh no-no-no, no. no, no, no, i just, i just need a pretend ticket. ticket counter attendant: i\u0092m sorry sir, i don\u0092t understand.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " what would you give to a kid if he wanted a ticket to play with? ticket counter attendant: are you travelling with a child?", "answer": " no. all right, y\u0092know what, she\u0092s  gonna think that i\u0092m handing you a credit card, but what i\u0092m really gonna do is hand you a library card. ticket counter attendant: ah, sir a ticket to yemen is $2,100 and we don\u0092t take library cards.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " what\u0092s the matter? is something wrong? do you have to stay?", "answer": "  american express?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " i can\u0092t believe they\u0092re doing that to him! i told them to go easy on him!", "answer": " no offence but, y\u0092know sometimes it\u0092s hard to understand you, y\u0092know with the accent, so\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " did you see me? i was pretty good, huh? that is one fun game!", "answer": " right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": "  hey, could you do me a favour? could you just grab me a bottle of water?", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " thanks.  i-i think i\u0092m dying. i really do.", "answer": " oh, poor baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": "  tell my son that i love him.  excellent! well, okay, i gotta have some more fun!", "answer": " ross, they are killing you out there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": "  that\u0092s not true!", "answer": " she\u0092s right! you have to stop!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " what? no! no, i\u0092m not stopping. i\u0092m red ross!", "answer": " dude, if you go back out there, you\u0092re gonna be dead ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " i don\u0092t care! i am not quitting! i insist on finishing this game!", "answer": " all right, all right, if you insist on doing this, at least let me help you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " no, god no! that is no place for a woman. those guys will grab anything.", "answer": " no. that\u0092s not what i\u0092m saying. i just may know a few things that might help you inflict some pain.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i like that.", "answer": " yeah? listen closely, devon has got a weak ankle.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " huh?", "answer": " one swift kick and he\u0092ll back off.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " all right, bad ankle, got it!", "answer": " and that big bloke with the beard, he has got a trick hip. yeah. and uh, and david over there, i heard he doesn\u0092t wear a cup.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " yeah? i can use that, trick hip, no cup, okay! okay!", "answer": " and uh, liam, liam\u0092s got bad knees. you hit him right and he\u0092ll go down like a lamp.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " but-but, liam\u0092s on my team.", "answer": " i don\u0092t care! you just get him!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": "  what-what are-what are these?", "answer": " oh, just some pictures i made and hung up. i thought they\u0092d brighten up the place. they do don\u0092t you think?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " oh my god! look at this!", "answer": " okay, but there is a wire back there! i mean that switch is connected to something!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " i don\u0092t care! the wires have come loose in your head!", "answer": " i just thought that if i could follow the wire i could find out what it did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " and did you?!", "answer": " no. it disappears back there behind that baseboard. for a minute there, i thought it went downstairs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " but it didn\u0092t. say hello to mrs. chatracus.", "answer": " oh my god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " hello darling.", "answer": " hello, mrs. chatracus.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " now, are you sure you don\u0092t want to go see a doctor?", "answer": " oh no! that-that\u0092ll just bring me down! this was great! i mean i-i-i was great! this is a great day! y\u0092know what? i\u0092m buying everyone coffee. all right? if someone would just grab my wallet, it\u0092s in my pocket.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " yeah, sure.", "answer": " no, not you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " uhh, look, your eye\u0092s still popping out a little, i\u0092m gonna go get some ice.", "answer": " ooh, ice! i am so in the mood for ice!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " you were amazing out there.", "answer": " oh, i kinda was, wasn\u0092t i?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " i made a man twice my size cry. i mean, i haven\u0092t done that since i was four and i washed my dad\u0092s porsche with rocks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " you really enjoyed yourself didn\u0092t you?", "answer": " please! are you kidding? i-i hurt three huge men, i gave a guy a bloody nose\u0097i mean i-i\u0092m not proud of it but, i really am. and it\u0092s all because of you, wonderful, amazing you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " i think you\u0092ve got concussion.", "answer": " no, no, i\u0092m serious. thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " you\u0092re welcome.  i\u0092m sorry. did i hurt you?", "answer": " it\u0092s worth the pain.  y\u0092know what, you know what? it\u0092s not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": "  this is the final boarding call for flight 664 to yemen.", "answer": " well, i-i guess i gotta go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " oh, my bing-a-ling. i\u0092ll wait for you. do you even know how long you\u0092re going to be gone?", "answer": " well, just until we find an energy source to replace fuel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " oh. well, i\u0092ll right you everyday.  15 yemen road, yemen.", "answer": " okay, good-bye. good-bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " chandler?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " chandler!", "answer": " janice! there you are! there you are! i had to have one last kiss, and also-also you said that you were going to leave right after i got on the plane!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " no! no! i wanna see you take-off.", "answer": " well, i then guess i\u0092m going to yemen! i\u0092m going to yemen!  when we get to yemen, can i stay with you? closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " all right. the super couldn\u0092t figure out what it did. a $200 an hour electrician couldn\u0092t figure out what it did. i\u0092ve had seven pretty serious shocks. i officially give up.", "answer": " thank god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep15.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}]